https://www.blackrock.com/corporate/compliance/terms-and-conditions

Terms and conditions
Please read this page before proceeding as it explains certain restrictions imposed by law on the distribution of this information and the jurisdictions in which our products and services are authorised to be offered or sold.
By entering this site, you are agreeing that you have reviewed and agreed to the terms contained herein, including any legal or regulatory restrictions, and have consented to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data as set out in the Privacy section referred to below.
By confirming below, you also acknowledge that you:
(i) have read this important information;
(ii) agree your access to this website is subject to the disclaimer, risk warnings and other information set out herein; and
(iii) are the relevant sophistication level and/or type of audience intended for your respective country or jurisdiction identified below.
The information contained on this website (this “Website”) (including without limitation the information, functions and documents posted herein (together, the “Contents”) is made available for informational purposes only.
No Offer
The Contents have been prepared without regard to the investment objectives, financial situation, or means of any person or entity, and the Website is not soliciting any action based upon them.
This material should not be construed as investment advice or a recommendation or an offer or solicitation to buy or sell securities and does not constitute an offer or solicitation in any jurisdiction where or to any persons to whom it would be unauthorized or unlawful to do so.
Access Subject to Local Restrictions
The Website is intended for the following audiences in each respective country or region: In the U.S.: public distribution. In Canada: public distribution. In the UK and outside the EEA: professional clients (as defined by the Financial Conduct Authority or MiFID Rules) and qualified investors only and should not be relied upon by any other persons. In the EEA, professional clients, qualified clients, and qualified investors. For qualified investors in Switzerland, qualified investors as defined in the Swiss Collective Investment Schemes Act of 23 June 2006, as amended. In DIFC: 'Professional Clients’ and no other person should rely upon the information contained within it. In Singapore, public distribution. In Hong Kong, public distribution. In South Korea, Qualified Professional Investors (as defined in the Financial Investment Services and Capital Market Act and its sub-regulations). In Taiwan, Professional Investors. In Japan, Professional Investors only (Professional Investor is defined in Financial Instruments and Exchange Act). In Australia, public distribution. In China, this may not be distributed to individuals resident in the People's Republic of China ("PRC", for such purposes, excluding Hong Kong, Macau and Taiwan) or entities registered in the PRC unless such parties have received all the required PRC government approvals to participate in any investment or receive any investment advisory or investment management services. For Other APAC Countries, Institutional Investors only (or professional/sophisticated /qualified investors, as such term may apply in local jurisdictions). In Latin America, institutional investors and financial intermediaries only (not for public distribution).
This Contents are not intended for, or directed to, persons in any countries or jurisdictions that are not enumerated above, or to an audience other than as specified above.
This Website has not been, and will not be submitted to become, approved/verified by, or registered with, any relevant government authorities under the local laws. This Website is not intended for and should not be accessed by persons located or resident in any jurisdiction where (by reason of that person's nationality, domicile, residence or otherwise) the publication or availability of this Website is prohibited or contrary to local law or regulation or would subject any BlackRock entity to any registration or licensing requirements in such jurisdiction.
It is your responsibility to be aware of, to obtain all relevant regulatory approvals, licenses, verifications and/or registrations under, and to observe all applicable laws and regulations of any relevant jurisdiction in connection with your access. If you are unsure about the meaning of any of the information provided, please consult your financial or other professional adviser.
No Warranty
The Contents are published in good faith but no advice, representation or warranty, express or implied, is made by BlackRock or by any person as to its adequacy, accuracy, completeness, reasonableness or that it is fit for your particular purpose, and it should not be relied on as such. The Contents do not purport to be complete and is subject to change. You acknowledge that certain information contained in this Website supplied by third parties may be incorrect or incomplete, and such information is provided on an "AS IS" basis. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or delete, any content and the terms of use of this Website without notice. Users are advised to periodically review the contents of this Website to be familiar with any modifications. The Website has not made, and expressly disclaims, any representations with respect to any forward-looking statements. By their nature, forward-looking statements are subject to numerous assumptions, risks and uncertainties because they relate to events and depend on circumstances that may or may not occur in the future.
No information on this Website constitutes business, financial, investment, trading, tax, legal, regulatory, accounting or any other advice. If you are unsure about the meaning of any information provided, please consult your financial or other professional adviser.
No Liability
BlackRock shall have no liability for any loss or damage arising in connection with this Website or out of the use, inability to use or reliance on the Contents by any person, including without limitation, any loss of profit or any other damage, direct or consequential, regardless of whether they arise from contractual or tort (including negligence) or whether BlackRock has foreseen such possibility, except where such exclusion or limitation contravenes the applicable law.
You may leave this Website when you access certain links on this Website. BlackRock has not examined any of these websites and does not assume any responsibility for the contents of such websites nor the services, products or items offered through such websites.
Intellectual Property Rights
Copyright, trademark and other forms of proprietary rights protect the Contents of this Website. All Contents are owned or controlled by BlackRock or the party credited as the provider of the Content. Except as expressly provided herein, nothing in this Website should be considered as granting any licence or right under any copyright, patent or trademark or other intellectual property rights of BlackRock or any third party.
This Website is for your personal use. As a user, you must not sell, copy, publish, distribute, transfer, modify, display, reproduce, and/or create any derivative works from the information or software on this Website. You must not redeliver any of the pages, text, images, or content of this Website using "framing" or similar technology. Systematic retrieval of content from this Website to create or compile, directly or indirectly, a collection, compilation, database or directory (whether through robots, spiders, automatic devices or manual processes) or creating links to this Website is strictly prohibited. You acknowledge that you have no right to use the content of this Website in any other manner.
Additional Information
Investment involves risks. Past performance is not a guide to future performance. The value of investments and the income from them can fall as well as rise and is not guaranteed. You may not get back the amount originally invested. Changes in the rates of exchange between currencies may cause the value of investments to diminish or increase.
Privacy
Your name, email address and other personal details will be processed in accordance with BlackRock’s Privacy Policy for your specific country which you may read by accessing our website at https://www.blackrock.com.
Please note that you are required to read and accept the terms of our Privacy Policy before you are able to access our websites.
Once you have confirmed that you agree to the legal information herein, and the Privacy Policy – by indicating your consent – we will place a cookie on your computer to recognise you and prevent this page from reappearing should you access this site, or other BlackRock sites, on future occasions. The cookie will expire after six months, or sooner should there be a material change to this important information.
Confirm
Decline
Terms & Conditions
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Business Continuity
Business Continuity
© 2020 BlackRock, Inc. All rights reserved.
